[Music]
why wouldn't you just swallow normally I
I do
swallow okay um I have Cooper here for
his interview great and can I just say
again that normally I do swallow okay
Cooper it's nice to meet you yes nice to
meet you Michelle
firm you too you have powdered sugar all
over your face oh I guess that's why you
put observing as one of your skills on
your resume you leave it there the whole
time
no I see you guys have balls here
instead of chairs yeah we feel it's
better for the mind and the body I
prefer a walking desk that's what I have
at home put it at Point 6 and by the end
of the day I've walked about 8 Miles I
usually just go for a 9M run before I go
to work you know get the heart pumping
more cardiovascular benefits well some
say light to moderate exercise
throughout the day is best some say it's
worse
H my abs are engaged already
congratulations on getting engaged take
it where you can get it
huh so you want to recruit here at spark
I do and you went to Princeton undergrad
and Yale grad sumat sumti par for the
course oh where did you go to school
Michelle William and Mary I guess not
everyone can be quite up to par then huh
what's the Y mascot anyway an
it's a bulldog oh I would have guessed
what's the William and Mary
mascot someone who couldn't get any
Y no it's well it was the tribe but they
had to change it so now it's like a it's
like a bird sounds very inspiring since
you seem to think you know more than me
how about we see who can take into
account more factors in the fairly
simple interview question how many
pingpong balls can fit into a 747 fine
I'll go first in order to calculate the
number number of pingpong balls that can
fit into a 747 first you have to
calculate the average volume of a
pingpong ball point the size of a 747
point the number of seats in a 747 Point
whether those Steward is foldy up seats
are up or down therefore taking up more
space you mean jump seats yes Point
luggage compartments both overhead and
below the plane Point bathroom Point
waste container Point kitchen area Point
uh but technically it's called a galley
technically you're a g stop stalling
microwave oven in the kitchen area point
the refrigerator in the kitchen area
point the coffee pot in the kitchen area
point the cockpit Point uh the place out
of areas we've covered every area you
forgot one small detail impossible
pingpong balls aren't flat they won't
lie on top of each other seamlessly you
forgot to take into account the space
between pingpong balls you forgot to
take into account steer packing guess
you win I guess I do win we should make
out now yes we
should
did I get the jump no of course
not
no there's a man named Salazar on the
phone for you oh great put them
[Music]
through